signaltrader.com 2016-11-07

# Signal Trader Privacy Policy

##  The Signal Trader Privacy Policy 

I.S. Signal Trader Limited (Hereinafter "Signal Trader", "the Company", “us” or "we") is the owner of this website SignalTrader.com ("the Website"). Signal Trader understands you want to keep your information private, safe and discrete, and is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, store and use information on individuals that use this Website, and is designed to help you decide whether to use the Website and in what manner.

**Consent to use Information**

This Policy is a legally binding agreement between you (“you” or “user”) and us. By accessing the Website or providing information to us in other formats, you agree and accept the terms of this Privacy Policy as amended from time to time and you consent to the collection and use of information in the manner set out in this Policy. We encourage you to review this Policy carefully and to periodically refer to it so that you understand it and its subsequent changes if any. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE STOP USING THE WEBSITE IMMEDIATELY.

The definitions in the  Terms and Conditions \- apply to this Privacy Policy unless stated otherwise. IN ADDITION TO THIS POLICY, PLEASE REVIEW OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS WHICH ARE INCORPORATED HEREIN BY REFERENCE, TOGETHER WITH SUCH OTHER POLICIES OF WHICH YOU MAY BE NOTIFIED OF BY US FROM TIME TO TIME.

**What Information Does Signal Trader Collect?**

We collect two types of data and information from you:

**(1)** **Non-Personal Information** \- Signal Trader retains some non-personally identifiable information (“Non-Personal Information”), such as your approximate geo-location, your web request, browser type, browser language, web pages you visit before or after visiting our Website, URL’s, platform type, clicks number, landing pages, viewed pages and the order of those pages, activities on those pages and time spent on pages. This information is collected and retained for security reasons and so that we can audit and track statistically usage, audit our affiliates and calculate payments to third parties.

**(2)** **Personal Information** \- “Personal Information” is information that may be of a private or sensitive nature. Some of the Personal Information is collected from you when you create an account on the Website and submit your information and some while you are using the Website. Such information includes your name, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address and IP address.

We treat any Non-personal Information which is specifically connected or linked to any Personal Information as Personal Information.

**Mandatory and Optional Information**

In order to access our services on the Website, users may be asked to fill in a form providing some personal information to the Company. Answers to questions on Personal Information are not mandatory unless the fields are marked with an asterisk. Not supplying the information required in optional fields shall not represent any reduction in the services and information that we provide. However, failure to complete mandatory fields or providing incorrect Personal Information may prevent us from fully providing the requested information or services.

**What is the Purpose of Collecting this Information?**

We collect the information outlined above in order to provide you with a better service. Non-Personal Information is collected for research and statistical purposes, to enable us to develop, customize and improve the Website, based on your preferences, usage and interactions with the Website, to process your requests for information, and to provide you with the most relevant services and offers.

Your Personal Information is collected to enable us to provide you with more relevant features, capabilities, offers and marketing materials we or our partners think you may be interested in, including based on your information, and it also allows us to provide you with technical assistance and support.

**Who Else Receives this Information (“Recipients”)?**

We may share or transfer information, including Personal Information, internally within our group of companies.

We share Personal and Non-Personal Information with third parties, when this is required in order to provide, maintain or improve our services and operation. This is the case with third party affiliates; we share your information with third parties for the purpose of providing you with offers we or such third parties think you may be interested in.

We share your Personal and Non-Personal Information with (i) third parties which provide services to the Company in order to allow or enable us to provide you with our services; (ii) third parties who provide the Company services in relation to the operation of the Website; (iii) any auditors, contractors or other advisers auditing any of the Company’s business processes; and (iv) any potential purchasers or investors in the Company.

Signal Trader may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your express consent.

Any processing performed by any Recipients will, where required by law, be governed by a data processing agreement in the form required by law, preserving any and all of your statutory data protection rights and obligating the Recipients to respect the Personal Information and handle it in accordance with the relevant laws. We also assure you that the Recipients are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information and to use your Personal Information only in the course of providing the aforementioned services and only for the purposes that Signal Trader dictates.

We may also share your Personal Information and other information in special cases if we have a good reason to believe that it is necessary to: (i) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (ii) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, violation of our policies or technical issues; (iii) enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy or any other agreements between you and Signal Trader, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of the Company, its partners, its affiliates, users or the public.

**Direct Marketing**

We may share your e-mail address and phone number with our marketing partners and may periodically use it ourselves for the purpose of providing you with marketing offers.. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers by sending a blank message with the word "Remove" in the subject area to  [support@signaltrader.com](mailto:support@signaltrader.com). If you unsubscribe we will remove your e-mail address from our marketing distribution lists and from any future lists we may share with our marketing partners. However, you may need to separately unsubscribe from marketing offers sent by our marketing partners.

**Right of Information**

The collection and processing of Personal Information is aimed at providing you with services offered by the Website and to send you marketing offers on products or services we think may be relevant to you. The Company will store this data as long as we believe it to be necessary and appropriate in order to provide and manage our services.

**Rights of Access, Rectification, Cancellation and Objection**

You have the right to access, correct, update or object to the usage of your Personal Information by making a written request to Signal Trader using our  contact us page \- . Your requests will be dealt with in a prompt and professional manner.

**Security and confidentiality**

The Company guarantees that your Personal Information will be treated with confidentiality, and that the server in which this data is to be stored has implemented the necessary industry-standard security measures to prevent accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access. However, we cannot completely guarantee the security of your information, which might be accessed, disclosed, modified, or destroyed, and it should be emphasized that you share this information at your own risk.

**Cookies**

Non-Personal Information is collected, inter alia, through the use of cookies. “Cookies” are small bits of code, usually stored on a user's computer hard drive, which enable a website to remember user preferences. Cookies are very helpful and can be used for various different purposes. These purposes include allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your credentials and preferences, and making the interaction between you and the Website quicker and easier. Cookies are also used to help ensure that the content you see online is relevant to you and your interests. You can find more information about cookies at  [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Although the use of cookies is generally harmless, some people may find it intrusive and may wish to block some or all cookies, or delete cookies that have already been set. You can modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for instructions on how to do so correctly. However, you should bear in mind that, by deleting or blocking cookies, some of the features may not work properly or as effectively.

The cookies on this website are used to hide certain publicity from the users that have chosen this option. The cookies are also used to save the credentials and preferences of the user in order to allow automatic login to the private home page of the registered user, but only if this is desired.

**Links to other website**

This Privacy Policy applies only to this Website. This Policy does not apply to third party websites, linked to our Website.. Third party websites or services may have their own privacy policies and we advise you to read them carefully. Inclusion of a link to a third party website or service is not a recommendation of such a website or service. Third party sites may contain information or service that is illegal, or that some people may find inappropriate or offensive. Before using third party sites and services or before making a purchase, we recommend you to read and understand the privacy policy and terms and conditions of such third party websites and services and warranty for purchased products. You are knowingly and voluntarily assuming all risks of using third party sites to purchase products and services. You acknowledge and agree that we shall have no liability whatsoever with respect to such third party sites and your usage of them.

**Assignment**

We may transfer or assign your information, without any notice, and without a need to receive your consent, to any third party as a result of change of control, consolidation, merger, acquisition or reorganization. You acknowledge that in the event of bankruptcy, insolvency or receivership, we may have no control over the use and transfer of your Personal Information.

**Updates to this policy**

This Privacy Policy is subject to modifications. Please check the "Last Modified " heading at the bottom of this document to see when this Privacy Policy was last updated. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. Your use of the Site or Services, or your provision of personal information following any changes means that you accept the updated Privacy Policy.

**Last Modified** : 25.2.2014
